Suppose you were able to stop time for three minutes.
What would you do?
Moritani?
Huh?
Come on, were you not listening?
Oh, s-sorry, I was spacing out.
You see, I've read short stories by that author before.
R-Really?
I was thinking of reading one of their novels next.
You got any recommendations?
Uh, I... Um...
Um...
It was...
It was as a fleeting dream...
Huh? Why aren't you frozen?
What is eternity like?
I stopped time...
Did you do this?
And then I got found out...
H-How did you know—
And wait, Murakami, how come you can move?
Can you stop time for as long as you want?
J-Just three minutes.
Three minutes, huh?
That's short.
You went as far as to stop time
just to get a peek at my underwear?
Huh?
You're a real creep, aren't you?
N-N-No, that's not what I—
Wonder how people would react if I told them.
How the normally timid, inconspicuous Moritani...
...is actually a creep who goes around looking at other girls' underwear.
No, wait! I'll do anything you want!
I had no idea...
Anything?
...Murakami was like that.
You'll really do anything?
She's a bit mean.
But... Even so...
She's so pretty that I get nervous around her.
What should I have you do?
I'll think of something for tomorrow.
She'll "think of something"?
I wonder what she'll make me do...
Good morning, Moritani!
Ah! I'm sorry!
Huh?
Uh... G-Good morning.
Something the matter?
No, it's nothing.
By the way, Moritani,
you haven't joined a club yet, have you?
Huh? No...
How about the ping pong club?
We're running low on members, see.
I mean... I'm already a second year...
No matter!
We're pretty easy-going,
so we don't mind people joining later.
Why don't you stop by after school?
Come on...
Why does she have to come talk to me every single day?
So if—
Oh?
You stop time over something like this?
And now you're off to look up girls' skirts, are you?
What? I-I wouldn't do that!
But you looked up mine yesterday.
I-I've never done that with anyone else.
Th-That was my first time...
Really?
Yes, really.
Well, that aside,
time really has stopped, huh?
It wasn't a dream after all.
I wish it was just a dream!
Am I the only one who can move?
I think so...
I wonder why it's just me.
I-I have no idea.
If I knew that, I'd make sure
Murakami was frozen too!
So you stopped time,
but I, and only I, can still move.
That's got to be because you're interested in me, no?
Huh?
You wanted to share this time with me,
and no one else.
That must be it.
In other words...
I can't...
You've got a crush on me.
I can't keep up with Murakami.
By the way...
You free this Sunday?
When was the last time I spent
my time off with someone?
Hey, you alone?
I'll take you somewhere fun.
Moritani!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, no, I...
Let's get this date started.
What?
D-Date?!
This is so good!
Here, try some.
Hurry up! It's melting!
Come on, here!
Like it?
Are you sure you wanted to come here?
I'm fine with wherever you want to go.
Y-Yeah.
I-I want to go where you want to go.
Really?
No need to worry about me.
Look at that girl! She's so pretty!
I know, right?
Wonder if she's a model or something.
I wouldn't be surprised.
I want to stop time and run away.
Hey, look! This would be perfect on you!
But...
I think I'll buy you a pair of these.
Wha—
She's not like other people.
They're the same ones I'm wearing.
Bet you want them.
I mean, you were staring at them real hard.
No! It's not the panties I'm interested in!
Not the panties, but?
Being with Murakami...
Oh yeah, it's me wearing these
that you're interested in.
There you go again...
is so much fun.
Fun?
Do I really deserve to have fun spending time with others?
Hm?
Hey, what do you think of this?
Huh?
It's Tamaki from our class.
Along with a girl from another class.
Th-They seem to get along well.
Think they're dating?
I wonder when they got together.
Wish he'd just told me.
What? Does she mean...
Murakami, were you and Tamaki...
We were going out.
Though I guess I'm not his girlfriend anymore.
What? So he got together with another girl in secret?
No, that can't...
Let's go.
What?
What?!
Are you sure about this?
I mean, if you two were going out,
that's awful of Tamaki!
You should tell him—
Not like I actually loved him or anything.
He just asked me to go out with him, so I did.
B-But then, what about your feelings?
They don't matter.
Murakami...
Why do you talk as if you've given up on everything?
Of course your feelings matter.
Moritani?
Time has...
Murakami! No one will know if you do it now!
Hurry!
Maybe Murakami is right.
The reason I'm still able to move when you stop time...
...is because I want to spend time together with Murakami.
So, in other words...
You've got a crush on me.
We spent the following few days stopping time
and going around spying on our classmates' little secrets.
Murakami knows a lot about the other students.
Possibly even a bit too much.
Hey, are the three minutes up soon?
Yeah.
This is like our own secret time.
Makes me kind of excited.
Yeah, same here.
See?
Huh? I, uh...
Th-They're soft...
Too bad you can't stop time for longer.
Nice shot! Go!
Haruka! Mind joining our team?
Sure!
What? No fair!
Murakami, join ours instead!
No way, you've already got three basketball club members.
Haruka's worth ten people! That's not fair!
Everybody loves Murakami.
Nice shot, Haruka.
Thanks.
All right! One more rou—
Moritani.
Huh? What?
What's wrong? Why did you stop time?
Uh... Well...
I did it without thinking.
You were running around so much,
so I figured maybe you needed a break.
I see. Thanks.
What the heck am I doing?
Oh, I get it!
See? That's how you solve it in no time.
You're a lifesaver, thank you!
The hero we need!
Always saving our butts.
You're such a good teacher.
Sorry we're so dumb.
Thanks a lot.
Moritani.
S-Sorry.
I did it by mistake.
I see...
Murakami is loved by everyone, not just me.
W-Well, since time is already stopped and all,
could you help me with a problem?
I mean, sure. Which one?
Um, well, it's...
What the heck am I doing?
I can stop time all I want,
but I can't keep Murakami to myself.
Good morning, Haruka!
Morning.
Hey, did you hear about Tamaki?
Huh?
What?
What about him?
Oh yeah, you mean how he put a pair of panties on his head while on a date?
Seriously? What a freak.
Did you know about that, Haruka?
Oh, yeah, I heard it somewhere.
Man, who does that?
What's up, Moritani?
It wasn't on purpose.
It wasn't on purpose, although...
Th-That's strange...
My power's been acting up lately...
Or rather, my emotions have been acting up...
Why are you lying?
Are you jealous?
You were feeling lonely, so—
No, you're wrong! I'm not jealous!
Really, I swear, it's just by accident.
If you say so.
Moritani.
Yes?
If you are doing it on purpose,
you should probably stop.
"You should probably stop"...
What Murakami said...
...keeps turning over in my mind.
Murakami is probably fed up with me.
And that thought...
...scares me.
Days went by without anything being resolved.
May I go to the nurse's office? My stomach hurts.
What am I doing?
This is just stupid.
There's someone sleeping, so keep it down.
Okay.
You haven't been stopping time lately.
Why not?
Because you told me I should stop.
I don't want to get on your bad side.
You're blaming it on me?
No!
You have to come to terms with what you truly want to do.
What I truly want to do?
Yup.
I couldn't tell you that.
Why not?
If I did, you'd get upset.
You'd make me upset...
At that rate, you'll never be able to share your true feelings with anyone.
Isn't it almost time for class?
Once you're feeling better, you should head back to—
You're able to stop time for about three minutes, right?
Yeah.
So if I were to kiss you right here and now...
Time would start ticking again,
and the nurse would see us.
I don't mind, you know.
I'd be fine with someone seeing us kiss.
Once you're feeling better, head back to the classroom.
Okay!
Why don't you go out with me?
Go out?
If you go out with me,
I'll stop talking to other people.
In return...
In return?
...will you let me do something?
Moritani, remind me,
where'd you go for junior high?
Huh? Me?
Um... Well...
You went to a different school from us, right?
Y-Yeah, that's right.
Minami Junior High.
Oh yeah? There's not a lot of
people from Minami here.
R-Really?
Oh right, I finally got that lip balm everyone's been going on about.
Yeah?
The strawberry one.
Hey, Haruka. Could you help us with the homework for fifth period?
Not again!
You guys are too dependent on her.
Sorry.
Don't worry.
Hold on, I'll get my notebook.
You're the best!
In that case, I guess I'll join you.
You too?!
Who knew talking to people without stopping time
would be this draining?
Doesn't Murakami ever get tired of dealing with people?
Oh, come on! These false eyelashes come off too easy!
You just touch your face too much.
Gotta say though, that Moritani girl?
I wish she'd actually, like, reply to questions.
I know, right?
Whenever you ask her something,
she just goes quiet.
What's Haruka thinking?
Yeah...
But Murakami's always sucking up to people, isn't she?
Oh, I know what you mean.
Constantly trying to please others.
Always making eyes at guys too.
Did you hear about her and Yamaguchi,
the homeroom teacher?
What? How she lets him touch her?
Is that for real?
So that's why she gets special treatment.
Well, I wouldn't be surprised.
I mean, sure, it would be fun to be popular,
but Yamaguchi having his eyes on you? Screw that!
You reap what you sow, I'd say.
Oh, don't tell her I said that.
Yeah, I know.
I remember now.
This is why I can't get along with others.
All these superficial relationships.
I hated having to be with others so much,
that I lived my life running away.
But what about people who can't flee,
like Murakami?
Doesn't she have it even worse?
Okay, you can start.
Can you take my picture?
Picture?
Pay close attention to me.
Sure, I will.
I wouldn't take my eyes off you.
Come here.
Go ahead and satisfy your desire.
No one's watching.
Now's your chance.
When I touch her, I can feel her heart racing.
The beloved model student Murakami
wants to be a bad girl.
Murakami... Murakami...
You have to put your clothes back on!
Time will start ticking again!
Murakami almost looked disappointed.
As if she didn't mind being found out.
Will she do the same thing tomorrow too?
Murakami... Murakami...
Moritani!
Murakami?!
Um... I believe my name's Kobayashi.
S-Sorry...
Don't sweat it.
You have been spending
a lot of time with Murakami lately.
Are you joining the same club as her, or what?
Huh? No, not really.
Really?! Then have you given some thought to what I said about the ping pong club?
Ping pong?
Oh right, she mentioned something about that before.
I-I'm not really good at sports.
No worries!
See, it's also called table tennis,
and it's way easier to get into than other sports.
And just between you and me,
the school isn't really expecting anything from us.
Maybe I'll stop time and run away again...
You can start with practice swings!
No, I have to save my time for Murakami.
You're actually listening to what I have to say today, huh?
Huh?
Whenever I talk to you,
you always disappear somewhere.
I was worried I was bothering you or something.
S-Sorry, that wasn't my intention...
That's a relief.
Let's eat!
Moritani, you've got strawberry milk!
Mind if I have some?
Oh, sure.
That's an indirect k—
Thanks!
Your food looks great. Wanna trade with me?
Sure, here you go.
H-How can they be so intimate?
Yukari, your octopus sausages are so cute!
Did you make the same for your siblings?
Yup! They really love these.
I wish I could be your little sister!
Making enough for you would kill me.
Is this what girls are like with each other?
So what's she like, really?
Huh? Sorry, what was that?
I mean Murakami.
She's kind of scary to talk to, you know?
Yeah, now that you mention it.
I don't think I've ever had a real conversation with her.
You seem pretty close to her, Moritani.
How'd you end up friends?
Uh... I'm not really sure...
I can't tell them
it's because I stopped time and looked up her skirt.
She seemed lonely...
I must be imagining it.
Haruka!
Sorry about tha—
Moritani?
Why did you stop time?
Suddenly feel like talking to me?
Or...
...is all.
Huh?
You looked sad, is all.
Sorry, that's just what it seemed like to me.
Every once in a while, you'll gaze off
into the distance, you know?
I was thinking maybe that's a sign that you're tired or something.
You've seemed really busy lately.
Oh yeah, I never sent you the photos from when we stopped time the other day.
I don't want them.
I'd like you to keep them.
To remind yourself that it really happened.
Haruka, when did you get over there?
Huh?
You just disappeared from your desk with a poof.
That's silly.
Let's head home.
Y-Yeah.
"To remind yourself that it really happened."
Moritani? Moritani!
Moritani!
Are you not feeling well?
Wanna stop by the nurse's office?
I-I'm fine.
How about some fresh air, then?
Come on, let's go.
Huh?
O-Okay.
I feel so much better.
Maybe you were running low on oxygen.
What did you put down for your career plans?
Nothing yet.
What about you?
What?! A comic artist?!
Shh! Keep it down!
S-Sorry.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Everyone else is probably planning on going to university,
but I figured I might as well give it a try
before I start looking for a job.
That's incredible, Kobayashi.
Nah, I'm just naive.
I'm writing a ping pong manga right now.
I'm using my club experience to make it as realistic as I can.
Huh...
Career plans...
I...
...don't even know what will happen today.
Isn't that someone's career plans form on the floor?
It's Kobayashi's.
A comic artist?
Seriously? Lemme see.
No way, is that really what she's planning on doing?
Sounds good to me. Make a hit and she'll be rich.
Nothing about university.
Giving up on studies, huh?
Got her head in the clouds.
Moritani!
Murakami, wait!
Remember what I promised when we agreed to go out?
I said I wouldn't be alone with anyone other than you.
I've been keeping that promise.
Whenever I'm talking to someone,
I make sure to bring someone else into the conversation so we're not alone.
But I guess I was the only one who cared.
No, you're wrong, Murakami! Look!
I'm always thinking about you.
Just take these panties.
I bought these online because
I wanted to wear a matching pair.
No kidding.
We match.
She really is crazy.
But seeing Murakami smile like that,
I was so happy that I didn't even care anymore.
Three minutes.
That's how long my and Murakami's world lasts.
If only it could last longer.
Forever, without any limits.
Our three minutes are almost up.
Time is about to start ticking again.
Don't worry.
Look, everything's still frozen in time, isn't it?
You're right.
While time is stopped,
there's also nothing to move time forward.
There never was any time limit to begin with.
Oh yeah, now that you mention it, you're right.
That makes sense.
Does that mean time is stopped forever?
That's right.
Look.
Waves, stars, sand, and people.
They're all frozen in time.
And no clock is awake to count to three minutes.
They're stopped for eternity.
What is eternity like?
Does the thought make you lonely?
No, not as long as I have you!
But in reality,
my power to stop time was growing weaker,
and little by little, things began to fall apart.
She flashed her panties in the hallway?
For real?
Yeah, it's true. You saw it too, didn't you?
Yeah, that was definitely Murakami.
Haruka did?
Apparently, yeah.
Out of nowhere, with guys in the hallway.
Seriously? Is she a flasher, or what?
Pretty people can get away with anything.
She's kinda been weirding me out for a while,
but this is too much.
And they say she's seeing Yamaguchi,
the homeroom teacher.
Gross.
I don't know what to do.
On your mark.
Thank you so much for yesterday.
Huh?
For finding my career plans form.
I know becoming a comic artist is pretty unlikely,
but it's been my dream ever since I was a kid.
Mind if I ask something weird?
Huh?
So this is just a hypothetical...
What is it? Just tell me!
Say I had someone important to me,
and I thought I had the power to protect them,
but then I became unable to use that power...
A prince paying the medical fees for his frail lover
goes bankrupt!
Now what does he do?!
Something like that?
Huh? Y-Yeah, something to that effect.
Nothing he can do in that case.
The prince will just have to come clean to his lover.
Huh? Was I too blunt there?
No, it's just...
What if that lover didn't care about anything but the money?
Seriously? What a lowlife!
He should break up with her, pronto!
Gold diggers are the absolute worst!
Oh, but she supports him in some ways.
Really?
Maybe I'm imagining it...
Which is it?!
Um...
The prince has fun when he's with his lover,
and when she smiles, he's happy.
So he still wants to be together with her.
Right...
So you're saying they both need each other?
Isn't that what you call mutual love?
R-Really?
I bet she wants the prince to take it easier on himself and just talk to her.
You wouldn't be talking about Murakami, would you?
What? N-No, it's just a hypothetical!
Yeah, I know.
But I'm really glad that you
decided to ask me for advice.
I never expected that.
And I never thought I'd be able to
talk to someone this casually.
It must be thanks to spending time with Murakami.
There's something I need to tell you.
I'm not interested.
Wait!
Murakami!
I might lose my power to stop time!
What?
I can't stop time as easily as before.
And the length of time is decreasing.
So we won't be able to go wild like before, then.
I'm sorry.
You're still wearing your indoor shoes, you know.
That's just because you ran off without warning!
While you're still able to stop time,
let's leave behind proof that we were here.
Together.
Aikawa's copying this part wrong!
I'll fix it for her.
W-Won't she find out?
You think?
Aikawa isn't the type to worry about details.
I give her a 50% chance of noticing.
I'll also write that she needs to be careful sleeping up front or she'll be caught.
Wait, what are you—
Too late.
During the days that followed,
Murakami didn't do anything particularly outrageous.
Hey, who did this?!
Huh? What's up?
Someone's scribbled in my notebook.
"If you use your birthday as your password, your boyfriend will open the lock."
The heck's this?
I don't understand what she's trying to do.
She'll undress in the classroom,
and leave behind notes for people to find.
That's right. Well done memorizing that.
Now, on to the next task...
See? He touched her shoulder.
Doesn't that bother Murakami?
A panty flasher like her wouldn't care.
And she was kind of provocative to begin with.
Stop. I don't want to hear. I don't want to know.
I'm telling you, I don't know.
No use hiding it, Tamaki.
You used to date Murakami, right?
Well, thing is,
even when we were dating,
it didn't really feel like she cared about me.
What about you, Moritani?
How do you feel about me?
I'll suddenly kiss you, show you my underwear,
tell you to go out with me,
take my clothes off in the classroom...
I'm sure you were thinking the same thing.
Who would do this?
I've tried to go along with people's wishes as best I can.
"Show me your homework."
"Explain this part."
"Help me carry this."
"Go out with me."
"Something came up, can we reschedule?"
I went along with all of it, and this is what I get.
Whenever I asked you to stop time,
you never asked why or what I wanted to do.
I can tell.
No one has any interest in knowing the true me.
That's right, I don't want to know.
I don't want to know what she's really like.
She's a bit mean, but she's actually kind.
Just when I think she's kind, she becomes distant.
And when I feel she's distant, next she...
I don't want to know. But...
Then I can't say I truly love Murakami.
I want to understand Murakami.
Murakami! Can I visit your place sometime?
Did you find it all right?
Y-Yeah, no problem.
P-Pardon the intrusion...
You can take it easy.
It's just the two of us until dark.
You okay with Darjeeling tea?
S-Sure. Thanks.
Don't go snooping around the room while I'm gone.
When was the last time
I was in someone else's room?
Murakami's room smells good.
You didn't touch anywhere funny, did you?
No, I didn't.
Really?
Not even the bed?
D-Did not!
A-Anyway, the reason I came over is because I wanted a chance to talk to you properly.
Otherwise we only really talk while time is stopped.
I wanted to get to know you a bit better.
Moritani.
Huh?
Come over here.
Come on.
Let's do what you want to do.
No need to hold back.
I don't like this.
I can't imagine that this is what you want to do.
Why do you do this, Murakami?
That's a strange question.
It's because this is what you want to do.
What I want to?
What is she saying?
Am I wrong?
Does she mean...
It's what you want to do.
Do you...
...only care about what others want?
I'm scared.
I don't want to ask.
But...
Murakami, why did you decide to go out with me?
Could it be that...
You thought I wanted you to go out with me,
and that's why you did it?
Give me a sec.
My mom's back.
She forgot something.
Don't go searching anywhere while I'm gone.
Especially not under the bed.
Don't go searching anywhere.
She likes this.
He likes that.
That girl likes this.
This boy likes that.
You'll be okay for dinner, then?
Yeah, no worries.
You make sure to eat too.
Yes, I know.
The names of every student and teacher.
On the backs are birthdays,
blood types,
likes and dislikes,
what makes them happy...
You memorize all of these,
and act according to them?
That's right.
Did you see yours?
Misuzu Moritani.
"The reason she is always reading books alone
is just that she is bad at talking to others."
"She will easily grow fond of anyone who talks to her nicely."
No, I—
"She is actually very interested in others."
"She just can't make the first move."
"As long as someone is nice to her,
it doesn't matter who it is."
"She wants to be the only one who understands that person."
"She just needs an exciting ingredient like a shared secret."
"If it is a girl, all the better."
"It doesn't matter who."
Stop it! That's not me!
That's how all the people around me were.
Friends are just tools high up in the social hierarchy
that you use as accessories
to make yourself look stronger.
Am I wrong?
What everyone is looking for
is someone kind, who they can rely on,
who will help them without complaining,
who won't say what they don't want to hear,
and who will do anything she's asked.
That's the Haruka Murakami they want.
But what about your own feelings?
You also have things you want to do, don't you?
Let's have a look.
Haruka Murakami.
Wants to be liked by everyone.
Tries to please everyone, disliked by no one.
And you see,
what happens then...
...is that she's...
...left with nothing.
If you just pretend you didn't see anything today,
we can go back to being
"two girls secretly in love" tomorrow.
Murakami can't fall in love with anyone or anything,
and even during the three minutes that time is stopped,
she has no idea what she wants to do.
Is she really happy like that?
I don't know.
It's not something an outsider like me could hope to understand.
It's impossible for anyone to truly understand someone else.
So...
So you'll just have to live with that?
I don't know.
But right now, our hands are firmly entwined.
So...
Huh? What are they doing?
Moritani?
You knew time was about to...
You can't run away today, Murakami.
I, Misuzu Moritani, as well as Haruka Murakami
have been stopping time to do
all kinds of crazy things together!
We scribbled in people's notebooks,
put panties on Tamaki's head after he cheated,
took off our clothes in the classroom...
What are you saying, Moritani?
If you tell them that, then we can't...
"We can't", what?
Complete your sentence, Murakami!
Murakami!
Wait! Tell me, Murakami!
You told me that you try to please everyone so that they'll like you.
That means you wouldn't want anyone to know what we've been doing, right?
But you didn't try to stop me just now.
Why not?
In reality, you want everyone to know your true self.
You want them to discover your true self.
You say nothing was left of Haruka Murakami after she adjusted herself to suit others?
There's nothing that you want to do?
That's a lie, I know it!
Shut...
I've seen just how selfish you can be.
You wanted someone to find that part of you more than anything!
Shut up!
What could you possibly know about me?!
Murakami...
You don't know the first thing about me,
so don't assume you know how I feel.
I mean, I don't even know how I feel myself.
These clothes look great on someone as pretty as you, Haruka.
Thank you, Auntie!
I wish I could wear these every day!
I don't know you fully either!
But there's more to me than what was written on your flash cards.
What?
And that goes for you too!
We both don't know much about each other,
yet you turn a blind eye to yourself,
and reserve your criticism for others.
Shut up!
You were just afraid of being in the same world as others,
so you ran away to your own little world!
You're scared of getting hurt!
So are you!
You get hurt when someone touches a sore spot!
Shut up!
You think letting others decide your actions for you means you won't get hurt?
But in reality you are choosing!
You're wrong!
Lifting your skirt in the hallway,
or undressing at school...
You mean you did all that because I wanted you to?
That's a lie! You're just blaming me for what you wanted to do yourself!
You're wrong!
You're wrong, you're wrong!
I...
I don't stand out from the crowd.
I perfect the personality desired of me.
I'm a good girl who doesn't upset anyone.
I was thinking the same thing!
I have to be like that, or no one will love me.
I love you.
In return for not getting close to anyone,
I don't get on anyone's bad side.
I shut myself away in my own little world,
never actually trying.
But you tried.
You shift blame onto others, and you're selfish.
But still,
you try to be a good girl.
You do your best to learn about those around you,
and make friends without alienating anyone.
You took that burden upon yourself,
without running away.
I really respect you.
I love you, Murakami.
I see now.
The reason I was able to enter your world
was because I wanted to share that time with you.
I'm the one who wanted it first.
I like you too, Moritani.
I...
love you.
A few months passed,
and I lost my ability to stop time.
Even if I don't want to deal with something,
I can no longer stop time and run away like before.
I've started trying to be in the same world as others.
I would be lying if I said it wasn't tough.
I've become one person among many.
I envy and get envied.
I misunderstand,
get misunderstood, and upset others.
And some don't even care about me at all.
But even so, I still pull through.
After all, this world
has someone I love.
It was as a fleeting dream,
but for the two of them,
the time they shared was most definitely real.