It's always something simple
Something stupid that sets it off
It's only natural you would feel hurt
These silence-filled conversations are so painful
I'm too bad with words
They just get in the way
I love you so much
But I can't express it right
This feeling is too much to bear
I'm not used to saying someone's dear to me
But now I'm able to, just for you
As long as you're there, smiling by my side
There's nothing else I could possibly need
Our first encounter set everything in motion
Though there may be days we hurt each other
My desire to be with you
Is the light that guides me towards a new future
I did my best to act strong
As though everything was fine
Hiding how terrible I truly felt
I faked a smile yet again
On nights when I can't see you
Loneliness befalls me
My love for you is what leaves me worried
This sadness is too much to bear
When I told you I wanted to protect you
I can't say part of me wasn't hesitant
But even so, I decided to have faith
I must hold this feeling close, lest it break
I've come to love you so, so much
Being with you makes me so, so happy
Even if we happen to face a setback down the line
I'll never again let your hand go
Our first encounter set everything in motion
Though there may be days we hurt each other
My desire to be with you
Is the light that guides me towards a new future